[Music]
Welcome to Business Center launch event
2025 release wave 1. In this session, I
will show you all localization related
to electronic documents we deliver in
this wave. Before I start, I just want
to remind you how we are working with
localization at all. So what we have we
have B app and on this B app we added
new app electronic documents core and
with this e document core we are
planning we planned actually to cover 80
90 even more more% of all these features
on the top of that we added different
connectors because connectors can be
different you can use one of them or you
cannot maybe you do not want to use
connectors at all so this is on you what
you want to use do you want to use only
core without connectors or you want to
choose one of these connectors and then
on the top of that we added PEL B3
format as a global format and this
format is available in all countries so
in all our
localizations this is what we have by
default everywhere but then we have
different localization apps on top of
that I will focus on three new we
deliver this wave and this is first Fura
in
Spain in Germany and PayPal, Pint and
Zed in Australia and New
Zealand. What you can do more if we do
not have Microsoft localization in some
of your countries, you can build your
own localization on top of this
functionality the same way as Microsoft
is doing because we do not do anything
different from what we expect from other
partners to deliver from their site.
Okay, let's look what we delivered. So,
I already show you now what you can
find. You can find all these three apps
on app source. They are already there
but by default they are pre-installed in
your localization. So when you open for
example Australia localization you will
find already installed e document format
for pint and zed the same in Germany for
exec and factoria in Spain. So they're
there by default but if you accidentally
remove or whatever you can find all of
them on app source and you can install
again. Okay, let's look deeper what is
there. First, electronic documents in
Germany, we have supported two types of
files, PayPal B3 and Excnong
UBL. This is currently supported in
Germany. And what do you need to do when
you open your electronic document
service assuming that you already have
this uh app installed, you will find in
document format, you will have extra
long or PayPal format. So you just need
to choose one of them and that's it.
Related to format that's it. But related
to localization there are some
additional things there. We have by
reference mandatory field in Germany.
This is in general required to have by
reference mandatory. So we just wanted
to support you to make this easier to
keep this field mandatory because in
some localization this is not required
to have by default. So you just need to
turn on and you cannot post documents
without bio reference panatory. But one
step more because in general you need to
fill in by reference on documents but as
there is situation that in Germany
especially you have uh specific
references for customers. We added new
functionality. So now you can choose by
reference as a first option your
reference that means one from a document
header or customer reference. This is a
reference configure on a customer card.
So there is new field in German
localization on customer card for
reference. If you have reference there
you just need to say okay from where I
want to collect uh references when I
create new document and that's it. All
other things are business as usual. So
there is no differences. You can send
you can receive documents without any
problem. Now let's switch to Spanish
functionality. In Spain we have fat a uh
supported format and again very similar.
Yes, even I didn't mention Ple is there
by default. So PEL is uh available in
all localizations because this is by the
default format in busy central. But you
can find fura a322
uh version. So this is there format is
ready and there is not any additional
spec uh specific uh configuration you
need to make a service only one specific
uh thing when you are working with
Spanish voicing is related with uh
credit memos when you are working sales
credit memo you need to fill in facura e
reason code you will find in credit memo
details uh fast tab this field so you
must choose this one you will find all
these options. So you must choose one of
these option because they are required
by the law in your sales create memos.
So this is only one specific additional
specific related uh to Spanish
electronic voices. or other things how
we are preparing files and so on you can
find on our official
documentation and the last one it
documents in Australia New Zealand as I
said purple pint and zed because purple
pint is a new format uh in Australia it
will be mandatory from May you could uh
use earlier but this is now new format
and we wanted to be proactive to deliver
the newest format glo uh in all
countries where this is required and
this type this is much easier to set up
because there is no specific situation
in Australia, New Zealand. You just need
to choose which format you want to use.
Actually, you must use but uh in some
situation maybe you want to deliver a
payle b in some other to some other
customers. But in general, you need to
set up uh to your service AZ and you can
choose any of uh service integrations
available in this moment. We have
another session about new connectors. So
in this moment there are four new four
connectors at all. You can choose one of
them and you can use them without any
problem. So now from this wave e
documents are officially available in B
central in Australia in New
Zealand. This is what we have about
localizations. I just wanted to show one
uh additional thing about localization.
This is not directly related with
localization because this is technical
improvements but it will have
repercussion on localizations. So what
is coming uh with this wave we deliver
availability to handle the PDFA formats.
So some of electronic document formats
are in PDFA uh format. So we couldn't
handle it earlier but now with this wave
we deliver plus support and we will
continue to work in enabling PDFA
formats in some other
countries. So that's it about
localization.
I'm inviting you to watch another
sessions related to electronic documents
because there are a lot of new features
uh in this wave. Please watch some of
them because we have six different
sessions in this PC bus launch event.
And yes, on the end, thank you for
watching this video.